export const data = [
    {
      question: "What is the capital city of Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Kandy",
      option2: "Colombo",
      option3: "Galle",
      option4: "Jaffna",
      ans: 2
    },
    {
      question: "What is the currency of Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Rupee",
      option2: "Dollar",
      option3: "Taka",
      option4: "Ringgit",
      ans: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Which ocean surrounds Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Pacific Ocean",
      option2: "Indian Ocean",
      option3: "Atlantic Ocean",
      option4: "Arctic Ocean",
      ans: 2
    },
    {
      question: "What is the main religion in Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Christianity",
      option2: "Islam",
      option3: "Hinduism",
      option4: "Buddhism",
      ans: 4
    },
    {
      question: "What is the national flower of Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Rose",
      option2: "Lotus",
      option3: "Water Lily",
      option4: "Jasmine",
      ans: 3
    },
    {
      question: "In which year did Sri Lanka gain independence from Britain?",
      option1: "1956",
      option2: "1948",
      option3: "1965",
      option4: "1931",
      ans: 2
    },
    {
      question: "Which animal is considered sacred in Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Tiger",
      option2: "Elephant",
      option3: "Monkey",
      option4: "Dog",
      ans: 2
    },
    {
      question: "Which language is not an official language of Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Tamil",
      option2: "English",
      option3: "Sinhala",
      option4: "Hindi",
      ans: 4
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the famous rock fortress in Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Sigiriya",
      option2: "Anuradhapura",
      option3: "Polonnaruwa",
      option4: "Dambulla",
      ans: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Which city is known as the cultural capital of Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Colombo",
      option2: "Kandy",
      option3: "Galle",
      option4: "Matara",
      ans: 2
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sri Lanka's main export product?",
      option1: "Oil",
      option2: "Tea",
      option3: "Gold",
      option4: "Cotton",
      ans: 2
    },
    {
      question: "Which Sri Lankan cricketer is known for the most international wickets?",
      option1: "Aravinda de Silva",
      option2: "Lasith Malinga",
      option3: "Sanath Jayasuriya",
      option4: "Muttiah Muralitharan",
      ans: 4
    },
    {
      question: "Which is the longest river in Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Mahaweli",
      option2: "Kelani",
      option3: "Kalu",
      option4: "Deduru",
      ans: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Which port city is located in Southern Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Jaffna",
      option2: "Trincomalee",
      option3: "Galle",
      option4: "Batticaloa",
      ans: 3
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the first female Prime Minister of Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Sirimavo Bandaranaike",
      option2: "Chandrika Kumaratunga",
      option3: "Ranil Wickremesinghe",
      option4: "D. S. Senanayake",
      ans: 1
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Sri Lankaâ€™s parliament building location?",
      option1: "Galle Face",
      option2: "Diyawanna Oya",
      option3: "Fort",
      option4: "Maradana",
      ans: 2
    },
    {
      question: "What is the national bird of Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Peacock",
      option2: "Junglefowl",
      option3: "Parrot",
      option4: "Eagle",
      ans: 2
    },
    {
      question: "What is the staple food of Sri Lankans?",
      option1: "Bread",
      option2: "Rice",
      option3: "Pasta",
      option4: "Corn",
      ans: 2
    },
    {
      question: "What is the official name of Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Republic of Sri Lanka",
      option2: "Democratic Socialist Republic of Sri Lanka",
      option3: "United Kingdom of Sri Lanka",
      option4: "Kingdom of Sri Lanka",
      ans: 2
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the Tamil festival celebrated in Sri Lanka?",
      option1: "Vesak",
      option2: "Sinhala New Year",
      option3: "Maha Shivaratri",
      option4: "Thai Pongal",
      ans: 4
    }
  ];
  